<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lab7</string>
    <string name="text">In a small town nestled between rolling hills and dense forests, there lived a curious child named Alice. Alice was not like other children; she had a boundless curiosity and a thirst for knowledge that knew no limits. Every day after school, instead of playing with other children, she would run to the town’s library to read books about the world beyond her small town. She read about ancient civilizations, scientific discoveries, and mysteries of the universe. Her favorite subject, however, was the ocean. Alice was captivated by the tales of explorers who ventured into the unknown depths of the sea, discovering strange creatures and underwater landscapes that looked like scenes from a dream.

One rainy afternoon, as Alice was reading an old book about marine biology, she came across a story that sparked her imagination. It was a tale of an ancient city hidden deep beneath the waves, a city that, according to legend, held treasures beyond imagination. But it was not the treasures that fascinated Alice; it was the thought of the forgotten knowledge and secrets buried within the city’s walls. Determined to learn more, she spent weeks researching everything she could find about underwater ruins, ancient myths, and deep-sea exploration.

Her parents noticed her growing obsession and were both worried and proud. They knew that Alice was no ordinary child. She was destined for something special, something beyond the simple life of their small town. They encouraged her curiosity but reminded her to stay grounded and remember the importance of balance in life. Alice, however, was unstoppable. She continued to read and dream, imagining herself as an explorer, uncovering secrets hidden from the world for centuries.

Years passed, and Alice’s dream grew stronger with time. She studied hard, excelled in her studies, and eventually earned a scholarship to a prestigious university where she could study marine biology and archaeology. She was one step closer to fulfilling her dream of uncovering the mysteries of the deep sea. Her journey was only beginning, but she knew that she was on the path to something extraordinary. And in her heart, she carried the dream of finding the lost city, the city that had inspired her as a child, the city that had ignited her passion and fueled her lifelong quest for knowledge.</string>
</resources>